A Guide to the Papers regarding William Faulkner's Travels 1950-1963
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers regarding William Faulkner's Travels, 1950-1963
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
7258-a
This holding consists of 49 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This holding was deposited by Mr. Blotner on August 7, 1963.
Scope and Content Information
This collection includes manuscript articles by William Faulkner, correspondence about and with Faulkner concerning many aspects of his travel arrangements, Foreign Service Dispatches for the State Department, and newsclippings. The selective listing below lists only items written by William Faulkner.
Contents List
- Manuscripts
  - Address by William Faulkner October 2, 1959, TMs (photocopy), 3 p. on 3 l.
    Given at the Closing Plenary Session of the Seventh National Conference of the U. S. National Conference of the U. S. National Commission for UNESCO in Denver.
  - "Impressions of Japan" August 1-21
- Letters of William Faulkner
  - Letter to [Muna] Lee June 29, 1954, TLS, 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to Mr. Howland August 15, 1954, TL (photocopy), 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Muna] Lee March 4, 1959, TL (photocopy)1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Muna] Lee August 22, 1960, TL (photocopy), 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Gerald] Maxfield September 4, 1960, TLS (photocopy), 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Richard] Phillips January 17, 1961, TL (photocopy), 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Muna] Lee March 2, 1961, 2 TL (photocopy), 3 p. on 3 l.
  - Letter to Muna Lee March 21, 1961, Telegram (photocopy), 1 p. on 1 l.
  - Letter to [Muna] Lee Sunday, TL (photocopy) 1 p. on 1 l.